<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software IP Detail Record Denial of Service Vulnerability</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-20160928-ipdr</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.0</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2016-09-28T14:32:42</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2016-09-28T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2016-09-28T16:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">A vulnerability in the IP Detail Record (IPDR) code of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected system to reload.



The vulnerability is due to improper handling of IPDR packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IPDR packets to an affected system. A successful exploit could cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.



Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.



This advisory is available at the following link:

https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20160928-ipdr["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20160928-ipdr"]



This advisory is part of the September 28, 2016, release of the Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication, which includes 10 Cisco Security Advisories that describe 11 vulnerabilities. All the vulnerabilities have a Security Impact Rating of “High.” For a complete list of the advisories and links to them, see Cisco Event Response: September 2016 Semiannual Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewErp.x?alertId=ERP-56513"].</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">This vulnerability affects the following products running a vulnerable release of Cisco IOS Software or Cisco IOS XE Software:



    Cisco cBR Series Converged Broadband Routers
    Cisco uBR7200 Series Universal Broadband Routers
    Cisco uBR7225VXR Universal Broadband Routers 
    Cisco uBR10000 Series Universal Broadband Routers


For information about which Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software releases are vulnerable, see the Fixed Software["#fixed"] section of this advisory.



Devices running an affected release of software are affected if the IPDR feature is enabled and if the IPDR exporter is started. IPDR exporter is not enabled by default. 



To verify the status of an IPDR exporter, use the show ipdr exporter command and verify that the exporter is started. The following example shows a Cisco uBR10000 router with the IPDR exporter started:


router#show ipdr exporter 
IPDR exporter is started.
Current parameters:
    KeepAliveInterval   :300  
    AckTimeInterval     :60   
    AckSequenceInterval :200



Determining the Cisco IOS Software Release
To determine which Cisco IOS Software release is running on a device, administrators can log in to the device, use the show version command in the command-line interface (CLI), and then refer to the system banner that appears. If the device is running Cisco IOS Software, the system banner displays text similar to Cisco Internetwork Operating System Software or Cisco IOS Software. The banner also displays the installed image name in parentheses, followed by the Cisco IOS Software release number and release name. Some Cisco devices do not support the show version command or may provide different output.

The following example identifies a Cisco product that is running Cisco IOS Software Release 15.5(2)T1 with an installed image name of C2951-UNIVERSALK9-M:


Router&gt; show version 
Cisco IOS Software, C2951 Software (C2951-UNIVERSALK9-M), Version 15.5(2)T1, RELEASE SOFTWARE (fc1)
Technical Support: http://www.cisco.com/techsupport
Copyright (c) 1986-2015 by Cisco Systems, Inc.
Compiled Mon 22-Jun-15 09:32 by prod_rel_team
.
.
.

For information about the naming and numbering conventions for Cisco IOS Software releases, see White Paper: Cisco IOS and NX-OS Software Reference Guide["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/intelligence/ios-ref.html"].

Determining the Cisco IOS XE Software Release
To determine which Cisco IOS XE Software release is running on a device, administrators can log in to the device, use the show version command in the CLI, and then refer to the system banner that appears. If the device is running Cisco IOS XE Software, the system banner displays Cisco IOS XE Software or similar text.

The following example shows the output of the show version command on a device that is running Cisco IOS XE Software Release 3.16.1aS:


Router&gt; show version
Cisco IOS XE Software, Version 03.16.01a.S - Extended Support Release
Cisco IOS Software, ASR1000 Software (PPC_LINUX_IOSD-ADVENTERPRISEK9-M), Version 15.5(3)S1a, RELEASE SOFTWARE (fc1)
Technical Support: http://www.cisco.com/techsupport
Copyright (c) 1986-2015 by Cisco Systems, Inc.
Compiled Wed 04-Nov-15 17:40 by mcpre
.
.
.

For information about the naming and numbering conventions for Cisco IOS XE Software releases, see White Paper: Cisco IOS and NX-OS Software Reference Guide["http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/about/security-center/ios-nx-os-reference-guide.html"].
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">No other Cisco products are currently known to be affected by this vulnerability.



Cisco has confirmed that this vulnerability does not affect Cisco IOS XR Software or Cisco NX-OS Software.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="4">There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="5">Cisco has released free software updates that address the vulnerability described in this advisory. Customers may only install and expect support for software versions and feature sets for which they have purchased a license. By installing, downloading, accessing, or otherwise using such software upgrades, customers agree to follow the terms of the Cisco software license:

http://www.cisco.com/en/US/docs/general/warranty/English/EU1KEN_.html["http://www.cisco.com/en/US/docs/general/warranty/English/EU1KEN_.html"]

Additionally, customers may only download software for which they have a valid license, procured from Cisco directly, or through a Cisco authorized reseller or partner. In most cases this will be a maintenance upgrade to software that was previously purchased. Free security software updates do not entitle customers to a new software license, additional software feature sets, or major revision upgrades.

When considering software upgrades, customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories and Alerts page["http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.

Customers Without Service Contracts

Customers who purchase directly from Cisco but do not hold a Cisco service contract and customers who make purchases through third-party vendors but are unsuccessful in obtaining fixed software through their point of sale should obtain upgrades by contacting the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC):

http://www.cisco.com/en/US/support/tsd_cisco_worldwide_contacts.html["http://www.cisco.com/en/US/support/tsd_cisco_worldwide_contacts.html"]

Customers should have the product serial number available and be prepared to provide the URL of this advisory as evidence of entitlement to a free upgrade.

&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd"&gt;

    
        
    
    
        Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software
        To help customers determine their exposure to vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software, Cisco provides a tool, the Cisco IOS Software Checker["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/selectIOSVersion.x"], that identifies any Cisco Security Advisories that impact a specific software release and the earliest release that fixes the vulnerabilities described in each advisory (“First Fixed”). If applicable, the tool also returns the earliest release that fixes all the vulnerabilities described in all the advisories identified (“Combined First Fixed”).

        Customers can use this tool to perform the following tasks:

        
            Initiate a search by choosing one or more releases from a drop-down menu or uploading a file from a local system for the tool to parse
            Enter the output of the show version command for the tool to parse 
            Create a custom search by including all previously published Cisco Security Advisories, a specific advisory, or all advisories in the most recent bundled publication
        
        To determine whether a release is affected by any published Cisco Security Advisory, use the Cisco IOS Software Checker["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/selectIOSVersion.x"] on Cisco.com or enter a Cisco IOS Software or Cisco IOS XE Software release—for example, 15.1(4)M2 or 3.1.4S—in the following field:

        
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            

            
            

        
    
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="6">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="7">The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerability that is described in this advisory. 
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="8">This vulnerability was reported to Cisco during the resolution of support cases.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="9">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.
</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20160928-ipdr</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software IP Detail Record Denial of Service Vulnerability</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
    <cvrf:Reference>
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewErp.x?alertId=ERP-56513</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Event Response: September 2016 Semiannual Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="IOS">
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="12.2CX">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)CX">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-200494">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)CX</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="12.2CY">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)CY">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-204827">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)CY</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)CY1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209004">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)CY1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.3S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.3(3)S7">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209093">Cisco IOS 15.3(3)S7</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.3(3)S8">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209268">Cisco IOS 15.3(3)S8</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.3(3)S6a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213023">Cisco IOS 15.3(3)S6a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.3(3)S9">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213032">Cisco IOS 15.3(3)S9</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.3(3)S10">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-220442">Cisco IOS 15.3(3)S10</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.3(3)S8a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-220673">Cisco IOS 15.3(3)S8a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="12.2SCH">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-116524">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-116531">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-193270">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH0a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-197486">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH0a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-198051">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH2a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-198424">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH2a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-201141">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH5">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-202723">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH5</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCH6">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209007">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCH6</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.4S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(2)S3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209096">Cisco IOS 15.4(2)S3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(2)S4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209097">Cisco IOS 15.4(2)S4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209099">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S0e">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209569">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S0e</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S5">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-211297">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S5</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S0f">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-212635">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S0f</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S6">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213794">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S6</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S7">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-220445">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S7</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S6a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-220675">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S6a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S8">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-227921">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S8</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S9">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-231448">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S9</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.4(3)S10">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-234927">Cisco IOS 15.4(3)S10</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.5S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(3)S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-204901">Cisco IOS 15.5(3)S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(1)S3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209103">Cisco IOS 15.5(1)S3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(2)S2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209105">Cisco IOS 15.5(2)S2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(2)S3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-211751">Cisco IOS 15.5(2)S3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(3)S0a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213000">Cisco IOS 15.5(3)S0a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(1)S4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-214479">Cisco IOS 15.5(1)S4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(2)S4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-216577">Cisco IOS 15.5(2)S4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="12.2SCI">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCI">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-200638">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCI</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCI1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-202566">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCI1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="12.2(33)SCI1a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209008">Cisco IOS 12.2(33)SCI1a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.5SN">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(3)SN0a">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209632">Cisco IOS 15.5(3)SN0a</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.5(3)SN">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213001">Cisco IOS 15.5(3)SN</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.6SP">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.6(2)SP3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-226165">Cisco IOS 15.6(2)SP3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVR">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVR1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277230">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVR1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVR2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277253">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVR2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVR3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-279337">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVR3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVR10">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-290618">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVR10</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVS">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277232">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVS1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-279335">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVS1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVT">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVT1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-280759">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVT1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVT2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-282026">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVT2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVT3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-284785">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVT3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVT4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286399">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVT4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVU">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVU1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-283833">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVU1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVU10">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-284291">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVU10</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVU2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-284566">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVU2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVU11">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286400">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVU11</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVU20">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-289270">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVU20</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVU21">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-290557">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVU21</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVV">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVV1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-284341">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVV1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVV2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286029">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVV2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVV3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286940">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVV3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVV4">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-289371">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVV4</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVW">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVW">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286451">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVW</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVW1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286844">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVW1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="15.1SVX">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVX">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286927">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVX</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="15.1(3)SVX1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-289301">Cisco IOS 15.1(3)SVX1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco IOS XE Software">
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="3.10S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.10.7S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213472">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.10.7S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.10.8S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-217260">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.10.8S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.10.8aS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-220687">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.10.8aS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.10.9S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-225337">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.10.9S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="3.12S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.12.4S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213474">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.12.4S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="3.13S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.4S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213475">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.4S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.5S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213557">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.5S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.5aS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-217261">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.5aS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.6S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-217262">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.6S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.7S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-217263">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.7S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.6aS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-220688">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.6aS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.6bS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-225568">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.6bS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.9S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-231454">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.9S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.13.10S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-234928">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.13.10S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="3.14S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.14.0S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-206178">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.14.0S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.14.1S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-206181">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.14.1S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.14.2S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-206191">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.14.2S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.14.3S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-206192">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.14.3S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.14.4S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-206193">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.14.4S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="3.15S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.15.0S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-206180">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.15.0S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.15.1S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-210079">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.15.1S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.15.2S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-212268">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.15.2S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.15.1cS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213700">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.15.1cS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.15.3S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213776">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.15.3S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.15.4S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-217264">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.15.4S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="3.16S">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.16.0S">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-210081">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.16.0S</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.16.0aS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213476">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.16.0aS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.16.0bS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213777">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.16.0bS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="3.16.0cS">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213778">Cisco IOS XE Software 3.16.0cS</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="16.1">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="16.1.1">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-212436">Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.1</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="16.1.2">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-213100">Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.2</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="16.1.3">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-214993">Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.3</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software IP Detail Record Denial of Service Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCuu35089</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCuu35089</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2016-6379</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-116524</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-116531</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-193270</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-197486</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-198051</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-198424</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-200494</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-200638</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-201141</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-202566</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-202723</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-204827</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-204901</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209004</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209007</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209008</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209093</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209096</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209097</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209099</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209103</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209105</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209268</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209569</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209632</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-211297</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-211751</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-212635</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213000</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213001</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213023</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213032</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213794</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-214479</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-216577</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-220442</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-220445</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-220673</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-220675</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-226165</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-227921</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-231448</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-234927</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-277230</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-277232</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-277253</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-279335</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-279337</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-280759</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-282026</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-283833</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-284291</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-284341</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-284566</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-284785</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286029</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286399</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286400</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286451</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286844</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286927</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-286940</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-289270</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-289301</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-289371</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-290557</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-290618</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-206178</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-206180</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-206181</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-206191</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-206192</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-206193</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-210079</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-210081</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-212268</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-212436</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213100</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213472</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213474</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213475</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213476</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213557</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213700</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213776</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213777</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-213778</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-214993</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-217260</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-217261</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-217262</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-217263</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-217264</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-220687</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-220688</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-225337</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-225568</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-231454</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-234928</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.8</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>6.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.
</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20160928-ipdr</URL>
        <Description>Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software IP Detail Record Denial of Service Vulnerability</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
