<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers Vulnerabilities</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>2.1</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2023-01-11T15:47:36</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>2.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2023-03-14T15:39:17</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated existing vulnerabilities to add hardware platforms and added CVE-2023-20118.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>2.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-03-07T17:33:55</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated to indicate that CISA has added some of these vulnerabilities to KEV.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2023-01-11T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2025-03-07T17:33:55</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
      <cvrf:Date>2025-03-07T17:33:57.3784249Z</cvrf:Date>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication or execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.

Cisco has not released software updates to address the vulnerabilities described in this advisory. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5 ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">CVE-2023-20025 affects all software releases that are running on the following Cisco products:
RV016 Multi-WAN VPN Routers
RV042 Dual WAN VPN Routers
RV042G Dual Gigabit WAN VPN Routers
RV082 Dual WAN VPN Routers

CVE-2023-20026 and CVE-2023-20118 affect all software releases that are running on the following Cisco products:
RV016 Multi-WAN VPN Routers
RV042 Dual WAN VPN Routers
RV042G Dual Gigabit WAN VPN Routers
RV082 Dual WAN VPN Routers
RV320 Dual Gigabit WAN VPN Routers
RV325 Dual Gigabit WAN VPN Routers</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.

Cisco has confirmed that these vulnerabilities do not affect the following Cisco RV Series Small Business Routers:

RV160 VPN Routers
RV160W Wireless-AC VPN Routers
RV260 VPN Routers
RV260P VPN Routers with PoE
RV260W Wireless-AC VPN Routers
RV340 Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers
RV340W Dual WAN Gigabit Wireless-AC VPN Routers
RV345 Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers
RV345P Dual WAN Gigabit PoE VPN Routers</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">The vulnerabilities are not dependent on one another. Exploitation of one of the vulnerabilities is not required to exploit the other vulnerability. In addition, a software release that is affected by one of the vulnerabilities may not be affected by the other vulnerability.

CVE-2023-20025: Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, and RV082 Routers Authentication Bypass Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, and RV082 Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input within incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass authentication and gain root access on the underlying operating system.

Cisco has not and will not release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability. However, administrators may disable the affected feature as described in the Workarounds ["#workarounds"] section.

Bug ID(s): CSCwd47551 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwd47551"]
CVE ID: CVE-2023-20025
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Critical
CVSS Base Score: 9.0
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H

CVE-2023-20026 and CVE-2023-20118: Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320 and RV325 Routers Remote Command Execution Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320 and RV325 Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input within incoming HTTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges and access unauthorized data. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials on the affected device.

Cisco has not and will not release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability. However, administrators may disable the affected feature as described in the Workarounds ["#workarounds"] section.

Bug ID(s): CSCwd60199 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwd60199"] and CSCwe41652 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwe41652"]
CVE ID: CVE-2023-20026 and CVE-2023-20118
SIR: Medium
CVSS Base Score: 6.5
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators can mitigate the vulnerabilities by disabling remote management and blocking access to ports 443 and 60443. The routers will still be accessible through the LAN interface after the mitigation has been implemented.
  Disable Remote Management
To disable remote management, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; General.
Uncheck the Remote Management check box.
  Block Access to Ports 443 and 60443
First, add a new service to the access rules of the device for port 60443. It is not necessary to create a service for port 443 because it is predefined in the services list.

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Service Management.
In the Service Name field, enter TCP-60443.
From the Protocol drop-down list, choose TCP.
In both of the Port Range fields, enter 60443.
Click Add to List.
Click OK.

Next, create access rules to block ports 443 and 60443. To create an access rule to block port 443, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Add.
From the Action drop-down list, choose Deny.
From the Service drop-down list, choose HTTPS (TCP 443-443).
From the Log drop-down list, choose Log packets match this rule.
From the Source Interface drop-down list, choose the option that matches the WAN connection on the device.
From the Source IP drop-down list, choose Any.
From the Destination IP drop-down list, choose Single.
In both of the Destination IP fields, enter the WAN IP address.
Click Save.

To create an access rule to block port 60443, repeat the preceding steps, but for Step 5, choose HTTPS (TCP 60443-60443) from the Service drop-down list.

Note: If a second WAN port is being used, two additional ACL rules need to be set up using the WAN number and IP address for the second WAN port.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">Cisco has not released and will not release software updates to address the vulnerabilities described in this advisory. Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320 and RV325 Routers have entered the end-of-life process. Customers are advised to refer to the end-of-life notices for these products:

End-of-Sale and End-of-Life Announcement for the Cisco RV016 Multi-WAN VPN Router ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/collateral/routers/small-business-rv-series-routers/eos-eol-notice-c51-736069.html"]
End-of-Sale and End-of-Life Announcement for the Cisco RV042 and RV042G VPN Router (all models) ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/collateral/routers/small-business-rv-series-routers/eos-eol-notice-c51-743070.html"]
End-of-Sale and End-of-Life Announcement for the Cisco RV082 Dual WAN VPN Router ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/collateral/routers/small-business-rv-series-routers/eos-eol-notice-c51-736749.html"]
End-of-Sale and End-of-Life Announcement for the Cisco RV320 and RV325 Dual Gigabit WAN VPN Router ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/collateral/routers/small-business-rv-series-routers/eos-eol-notice-c51-743069.html"]

When considering a device migration, customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the new products will be sufficient for their network needs, that the new devices contain sufficient memory, and that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new product. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is aware that proof-of-concept exploit code is available for vulnerabilities CVE-2023-20025 and CVE-2023-20026 that are described in this advisory.

In March 2025, the Cisco PSIRT became aware of additional attempted exploitation of some of these vulnerabilities in the wild. Cisco continues to strongly recommend that customers upgrade their hardware to Meraki or Cisco 1000 Series Integrated Services Routers to remediate these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">Cisco would like to thank Hou Liuyang of Qihoo 360 Netlab for finding and reporting CVE-2023-20025 and CVE-2023-20026.

Cisco would like to thank Wang Jincheng from X1cT34m Laboratory of Nanjing University of Posts and Telecom for reporting that CVE-2023-20026 also affected additional platforms and for reporting CVE-2023-20118.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers Vulnerabilities</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Small Business RV Series Router Firmware">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-183630">Cisco Small Business RV Series Router Firmware </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Small Business Routers RV042 Series Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwd47551</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwd47551</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2023-20025</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-183630</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>9.0</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators can mitigate the vulnerabilities by disabling remote management and blocking access to ports 443 and 60443. The routers will still be accessible through the LAN interface after the mitigation has been implemented.
  Disable Remote Management
To disable remote management, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; General.
Uncheck the Remote Management check box.
  Block Access to Ports 443 and 60443
First, add a new service to the access rules of the device for port 60443. It is not necessary to create a service for port 443 because it is predefined in the services list.

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Service Management.
In the Service Name field, enter TCP-60443.
From the Protocol drop-down list, choose TCP.
In both of the Port Range fields, enter 60443.
Click Add to List.
Click OK.

Next, create access rules to block ports 443 and 60443. To create an access rule to block port 443, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Add.
From the Action drop-down list, choose Deny.
From the Service drop-down list, choose HTTPS (TCP 443-443).
From the Log drop-down list, choose Log packets match this rule.
From the Source Interface drop-down list, choose the option that matches the WAN connection on the device.
From the Source IP drop-down list, choose Any.
From the Destination IP drop-down list, choose Single.
In both of the Destination IP fields, enter the WAN IP address.
Click Save.

To create an access rule to block port 60443, repeat the preceding steps, but for Step 5, choose HTTPS (TCP 60443-60443) from the Service drop-down list.

Note: If a second WAN port is being used, two additional ACL rules need to be set up using the WAN number and IP address for the second WAN port.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Small Business Routers RV042 Series Remote Command Execution Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwd60199</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwd60199</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2023-20026</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-183630</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>6.5</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators can mitigate the vulnerabilities by disabling remote management and blocking access to ports 443 and 60443. The routers will still be accessible through the LAN interface after the mitigation has been implemented.
  Disable Remote Management
To disable remote management, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; General.
Uncheck the Remote Management check box.
  Block Access to Ports 443 and 60443
First, add a new service to the access rules of the device for port 60443. It is not necessary to create a service for port 443 because it is predefined in the services list.

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Service Management.
In the Service Name field, enter TCP-60443.
From the Protocol drop-down list, choose TCP.
In both of the Port Range fields, enter 60443.
Click Add to List.
Click OK.

Next, create access rules to block ports 443 and 60443. To create an access rule to block port 443, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Add.
From the Action drop-down list, choose Deny.
From the Service drop-down list, choose HTTPS (TCP 443-443).
From the Log drop-down list, choose Log packets match this rule.
From the Source Interface drop-down list, choose the option that matches the WAN connection on the device.
From the Source IP drop-down list, choose Any.
From the Destination IP drop-down list, choose Single.
In both of the Destination IP fields, enter the WAN IP address.
Click Save.

To create an access rule to block port 60443, repeat the preceding steps, but for Step 5, choose HTTPS (TCP 60443-60443) from the Service drop-down list.

Note: If a second WAN port is being used, two additional ACL rules need to be set up using the WAN number and IP address for the second WAN port.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="3" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Small Business Routers RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Remote Command Execution Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwe41652</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwe41652</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2023-20118</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-183630</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>6.5</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators can mitigate the vulnerabilities by disabling remote management and blocking access to ports 443 and 60443. The routers will still be accessible through the LAN interface after the mitigation has been implemented.
  Disable Remote Management
To disable remote management, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; General.
Uncheck the Remote Management check box.
  Block Access to Ports 443 and 60443
First, add a new service to the access rules of the device for port 60443. It is not necessary to create a service for port 443 because it is predefined in the services list.

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Service Management.
In the Service Name field, enter TCP-60443.
From the Protocol drop-down list, choose TCP.
In both of the Port Range fields, enter 60443.
Click Add to List.
Click OK.

Next, create access rules to block ports 443 and 60443. To create an access rule to block port 443, do the following:

Log in to the web-based management interface for the device.
Choose Firewall &gt; Access Rules.
Click Add.
From the Action drop-down list, choose Deny.
From the Service drop-down list, choose HTTPS (TCP 443-443).
From the Log drop-down list, choose Log packets match this rule.
From the Source Interface drop-down list, choose the option that matches the WAN connection on the device.
From the Source IP drop-down list, choose Any.
From the Destination IP drop-down list, choose Single.
In both of the Destination IP fields, enter the WAN IP address.
Click Save.

To create an access rule to block port 60443, repeat the preceding steps, but for Step 5, choose HTTPS (TCP 60443-60443) from the Service drop-down list.

Note: If a second WAN port is being used, two additional ACL rules need to be set up using the WAN number and IP address for the second WAN port.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sbr042-multi-vuln-ej76Pke5</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
