<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Apache Struts 2 Command Execution Vulnerability in Multiple Cisco Products</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-20131023-struts2</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.1</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2013-10-23T15:46:45</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2015-10-12T12:30:06</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Added information about Cisco Unified CCE and Cisco PCCE.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2013-10-23T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2015-10-12T12:30:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Multiple Cisco products include an implementation of the Apache Struts 2 component that is affected by a remote command execution vulnerability. 



The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied
input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests
consisting of Object-Graph Navigation Language (OGNL) expressions to an affected system. An
exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the targeted system. 



Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability for all the affected products except Cisco Business Edition 3000. Cisco Business Edition 3000 customers should contact their Cisco representative for available options.



Workarounds that mitigate this vulnerability are not available.
This advisory is available at the following link:

https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-struts2["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-struts2"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">All software releases for the following Cisco products are affected by this vulnerability:


    Cisco Business Edition 3000
    Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) 
    Cisco Media Experience Engine (MXE) 3500 Series 
    Cisco Unified SIP Proxy (Cisco Unified SP) 
    Cisco Unified Contact Center Enterprise (Cisco Unified CCE) and Cisco Packaged Contact Center Enterprise (Cisco PCCE) 



Note: Cisco ISE Software is affected by additional vulnerabilities that are described in the Cisco Security Advisory at the following link:

https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-ise["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-ise"]



Cisco ISE customers should consult the advisory before making a decision on the upgrade path.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">The following Cisco products have been analyzed and are not affected by this vulnerability:


    
        Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software
        Cisco Business Edition 5000 and Cisco Business Edition 6000 Series
        Cisco Cloud Web Security
        Cisco Conductor
        Cisco Configuration Assurance Solution
        Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM)
        Cisco DVR
        Cisco Emergency Responder
        Cisco Firewall Service Module (FWSM) Software
        Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Fulfillment (HCM-F)
        Cisco Media Experience Engine (MXE) 3000 Series and Cisco MXE 5600 Series
        Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance 
        Cisco Prime Infrastructure
        Cisco Prime LAN Management Solution (LMS)
        Cisco Prime Network Control System (NCS)
        Cisco Secure Access Control Server (ACS)
        Cisco TelePresence Manager, Cisco TelePresence Recording Server and Cisco TelePresence Multipoint Switch
        Cisco Unified Attendant Consoles
        Cisco Unified Communication Domain Manager (CUCDM)
        Cisco Unified Communication Manager (CallManager)
        Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM and Presence Service and Cisco Unified Presence
        Cisco Unified MeetingPlace
        Cisco Unified Operation Manager (CUOM)
        Cisco Unified Services Monitor (CUSM)
        Cisco Unified Survivable Remote Site Telephony (SRST) Manager
        Cisco Unified Survivable Remote Site Voicemail (SRSV)
        Cisco Unity Connection
        Cisco Videoscape Control Suite
        Cisco Web Security, Cisco Email Security and Cisco Content Security Management Appliances
        Cisco WebEx
        Cisco WebEx Recording Format (WRF) and Cisco WebEx Network-Based Recorder (NBR) Player
        Cisco Wireless Control System (WCS)
        CiscoWorks Common Services

No other Cisco products are affected by this vulnerability.


</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">A vulnerability in the DefaultActionMapper component could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the targeted system.



The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests consisting of Object-Graph Navigation Language (OGNL) expressions. An exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the targeted system.



The impact of this vulnerability on Cisco products varies
depending on the affected product. Successful exploitation on Cisco ISE,
Cisco Unified SIP Proxy, and Cisco Business Edition 3000 could result in
an arbitrary command executed on the affected system. There is no
authentication needed to execute the attack on Cisco ISE, Cisco
Unified SIP Proxy and Cisco Unified CCE or Cisco PCCE. To exploit this vulnerability on Cisco Business
Edition 3000, the attacker must provide valid
credentials or persuade a user with valid credentials to execute a
malicious URL.



Successful exploitation on the Cisco MXE 3500 Series could allow the
attacker to redirect the user to a different and possibly malicious website; however, arbitrary
command execution is not possible on this product.



See the "Vulnerability Scoring Details" section of this security advisory for additional information regarding the attack vector and impact.



This vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug IDs CSCui22841["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCui22841"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) for Cisco ISE, CSCui33268["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCui33268"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) for Cisco Business Edition 3000, CSCui40582["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCui40582"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) for Cisco Unified SIP Proxy and CSCui48757["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCui48757"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) for Cisco MXE 3500 Series, and CSCui51516["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCui51516"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) for Cisco Unified CCE and Cisco PCCE.



This vulnerability has been assigned the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID CVE-2013-2251</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There is no workaround that mitigates this vulnerability.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability
for all the affected products except Cisco Business Edition 3000. Cisco
Business Edition 3000 customers should contact their Cisco representative for
available options.



When considering software upgrades, customers are advised to consult the Cisco Security Advisories and Responses archive at http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt["http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"] and review subsequent advisories to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution. 

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and  confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers. 

The following table provides the first fixed release for each of the affected products:




    
        
             Product
            First Fixed Release

            
        
        
            Cisco ISE1 
             1.0.4.573-6, 1.1.0.665-4, 1.1.1.268-6, 1.1.2.145-9, 1.1.3.124-4, 1.1.4.218-4 and 1.2.0.899

            
        
        
            Cisco Business Edition 3000 
             Not available - Please contact Cisco TAC or your Cisco representative for available options

            
        
        
            Cisco Unified SIP Proxy 
             8.5(5)
        
        
            Cisco MXE 3500 Series 
             3.3.2 and apply StrutsPatch.zip

            
        
        
            Cisco Unified CCE and Cisco PCCE 

            
            10.5(1), 8.5(4)ES37, 9.0(4)ES39, 9.0(3)ES13, 10.0(1)ES10, and 10.0(2) 
        
    



Note: The Engineering Special patch releases for Cisco Unified CCE are available at the following links:



8.5(4): http://www.cisco.com/cisco/software/special/release.html?config=2c8f679b8cdc4fed65e866e30fced34c["http://www.cisco.com/cisco/software/special/release.html?config=2c8f679b8cdc4fed65e866e30fced34c"]

9.0(4): http://software.cisco.com/download/special/release.html?config=b40f7ffb0a876e5dae4e202df4b6547b["http://software.cisco.com/download/special/release.html?config=b40f7ffb0a876e5dae4e202df4b6547b"]

9.0(3): http://software.cisco.com/download/special/release.html?config=593487b10e77653c20560c54efa6e7a0["http://software.cisco.com/download/special/release.html?config=593487b10e77653c20560c54efa6e7a0"]





1Cisco ISE is affected by additional vulnerabilities that are described in the Cisco Security Advisory at the following link:

https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-ise["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-ise"]



Cisco ISE customers should consult that advisory before making a decision on the upgrade path.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy[https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">Apache has confirmed this vulnerability at: http://struts.apache.org/release/2.3.x/docs/s2-016.html["http://www.nist.gov/cgi-bin/exit_nist.cgi?url=http%3A%2F%2Fstruts.apache.org%2Frelease%2F2.3.x%2Fdocs%2Fs2-016.html"]

 




 Code to exploit this vulnerability is publicly available from different sources over the Internet. Proof of concept code is also published on the official Apache Struts 2 page.


The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any malicious use of the vulnerability that is described in this advisory on any of the affected Cisco products. 
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">This vulnerability was reported to Cisco on Cisco Unified CCE and Cisco PCCE by Kevin Ostrin from Security Metrics.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.
</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-struts2</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Apache Struts 2 Command Execution Vulnerability in Multiple Cisco Products</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Name="Cisco" Type="Vendor">
      <Branch Name="Cisco Unified Contact Center Enterprise" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-7500">Cisco Unified Contact Center Enterprise </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Name="Cisco Identity Services Engine Software" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-111903">Cisco Identity Services Engine Software </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Name="Cisco Business Edition 3000 Software" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-114987">Cisco Business Edition 3000 Software </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Name="Cisco Unified SIP Proxy" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-195223">Cisco Unified SIP Proxy </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Name="Cisco MXE 3500 (Media Experience Engine)" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-195235">Cisco MXE 3500 (Media Experience Engine) </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Apache Struts 2 Remote Command Execution Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCui33268</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCui33268,CSCui22841,CSCui40582,CSCui48757,CSCui51516</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2013-2251</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-114987</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-195223</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-195235</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-7500</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>9.0</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>7.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:S/C:C/I:C/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-114987</ProductID>
      </ScoreSetV2>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>10.0</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>8.3</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:C/I:C/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-195223</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-7500</ProductID>
      </ScoreSetV2>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>4.0</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>3.3</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:S/C:N/I:P/A:N/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-195235</ProductID>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There is no workaround that mitigates this vulnerability.
</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20131023-struts2</URL>
        <Description>Apache Struts 2 Command Execution Vulnerability in Multiple Cisco Products</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
