<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Software Geolocation Remote Access VPN Bypass Vulnerability</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-ftd-ravpn-geobypass-9h38M37Z</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.0</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-08-14T15:53:33</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2025-08-14T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2025-08-14T16:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
      <cvrf:Date>2025-08-14T15:54:21.1733704Z</cvrf:Date>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">A vulnerability in the Geolocation-Based Remote Access (RA) VPN feature of Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured policies to allow or deny HTTP connections based on a country or region.

This vulnerability exists because the URL string is not fully parsed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP connection through the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured policies and gain access to a network where the connection should have been denied.

Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ftd-ravpn-geobypass-9h38M37Z ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ftd-ravpn-geobypass-9h38M37Z"]

This advisory is part of the August 2025 release of the Cisco Secure Firewall ASA, Secure FMC, and Secure FTD Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication. For a complete list of the advisories and links to them, see Cisco Event Response: August 2025 Semiannual Cisco Secure Firewall ASA, Secure FMC, and Secure FTD Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewErp.x?alertId=ERP-75415"].</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">At the time of publication, this vulnerability affected Cisco devices if they were running Cisco Secure FTD Software Release 7.7.0 and had Geolocation-Based RA VPN enabled.

The Geolocation-Based RA VPN feature is new as of Cisco Secure FTD Software Release 7.7.0. For configuration details, see Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Release Notes, Version 7.7.x ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/secure-firewall/release-notes/threat-defense/770/threat-defense-release-notes-77.html"] and Configure Geolocation-Based Policies for Remote Access VPN on Secure Firewall Threat Defense ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/docs/security/secure-firewall-threat-defense/222810-configure-geolocation-based-policies-for.html"].

For more information about which Cisco software releases are vulnerable, see the Fixed Software ["#fs"] section of this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by this vulnerability.

Cisco has confirmed that this vulnerability does not affect Cisco Secure Firewall Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="4">There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="5">When considering software upgrades ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.
Cisco Secure Firewall ASA, Secure FMC, and Secure FTD Software
To help customers determine their exposure to vulnerabilities in Cisco Secure Firewall ASA, Secure FMC, and Secure FTD Software, Cisco provides the Cisco Software Checker ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/softwarechecker.x"]. This tool identifies any Cisco security advisories that impact a specific software release and the earliest release that fixes the vulnerabilities that are described in each advisory (“First Fixed”). If applicable, the tool also returns the earliest release that fixes all the vulnerabilities that are described in all the advisories that the Software Checker identifies (“Combined First Fixed”).

To use the tool, go to the Cisco Software Checker ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/softwarechecker.x"] page and follow the instructions. Alternatively, use the following form to search for vulnerabilities that affect a specific software release. To use the form, follow these steps:

Choose which advisories the tool will search—all advisories, only advisories with a Critical or High Security Impact Rating (SIR) ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#asr"], or only this advisory.
Choose the appropriate software.
Choose the appropriate platform.
Enter a release number—for example, 9.16.2.11 for Cisco Secure Firewall ASA Software or 6.6.7 for Cisco Secure FTD Software.
Click Check.
  Only this advisoryAll Critical and High advisoriesAll advisoriesCisco ASA SoftwareCisco FMC SoftwareCisco FTD SoftwareAny Platform3000 Series Industrial Security Appliances (ISA)ASA 5500-X Series FirewallsASA Service ModuleAdaptive Security Virtual Appliance (ASAv)Firepower 1000 SeriesFirepower 2100 SeriesFirepower 4100 SeriesFirepower 9000 SeriesFirepower NGFW VirtualSecure Firewall 3100 SeriesFirepower Management Center Appliances




For instructions on upgrading a Cisco Secure FTD device, see the appropriate Cisco Secure FMC upgrade guide ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/security/defense-center/products-installation-guides-list.html"].

 Additional Resources
For help determining the best Cisco Secure Firewall ASA, Secure FMC, or Secure FTD Software release, see the following Recommended Releases documents. If a security advisory recommends a later release, Cisco recommends following the advisory guidance.

Cisco Secure Firewall ASA Compatibility ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/asa/compatibility/asamatrx.html"]
Cisco Secure Firewall ASA Upgrade Guide ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/asa/upgrade/asa-upgrade/planning.html"]
Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Compatibility Guide ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/secure-firewall/compatibility/threat-defense-compatibility.html"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="6">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="7">The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerability that is described in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="8">This vulnerability was found during the resolution of a Cisco TAC support case.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="9">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ftd-ravpn-geobypass-9h38M37Z</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Software Geolocation Remote Access VPN Bypass Vulnerability</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
    <cvrf:Reference>
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewErp.x?alertId=ERP-75415</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Event Response: August 2025 Cisco Secure Firewall ASA, Secure FMC, and Secure FTD Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software">
        <Branch Type="Product Version" Name="7.7">
          <Branch Type="Service Pack" Name="7.7.0">
            <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0</FullProductName>
          </Branch>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Firepower 1000 Series">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277393">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Firepower 1000 Series</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco 3000 Series Industrial Security Appliances (ISA)">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277438">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco 3000 Series Industrial Security Appliances (ISA)</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Firepower 9000 Series">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277440">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Firepower 9000 Series</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Firepower 4100 Series">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277441">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Firepower 4100 Series</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-277464">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Secure Firewall 3100 Series">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-286865">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Secure Firewall 3100 Series</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Secure Firewall 4200 Series">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-300754">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Secure Firewall 4200 Series</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
        <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Secure Firewall 1200 Series">
          <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303206">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Platform Cisco Secure Firewall 1200 Series</FullProductName>
        </Branch>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-277393">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:277393">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Firepower 1000 Series</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-277438">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:277438">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco 3000 Series Industrial Security Appliances (ISA)</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-277440">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:277440">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Firepower 9000 Series</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-277441">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:277441">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Firepower 4100 Series</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-277464">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:277464">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-286865">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:286865">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Secure Firewall 3100 Series</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-300754">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:300754">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Secure Firewall 4200 Series</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
    <Relationship ProductReference="CVRFPID-303356" RelationType="Installed On" RelatesToProductReference="CVRFPID-303206">
      <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-303356:303206">Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software 7.7.0 when installed on Cisco Secure Firewall 1200 Series</FullProductName>
    </Relationship>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Software Geolocation Remote Access VPN Bypass Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwo56698</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwo56698</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2025-20268</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:277393</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:277438</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:277440</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:277441</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:277464</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:286865</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:300754</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-303356:303206</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>5.8</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ftd-ravpn-geobypass-9h38M37Z</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Software Geolocation Remote Access VPN Bypass Vulnerability</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
