<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-20130821-hcm</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.0</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2013-08-21T14:21:47</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2013-08-21T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2013-08-21T16:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution (HCS) Assurance contains multiple vulnerabilities that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. Exploitation of these vulnerabilities could interrupt the monitoring of voice services and exhaust system resources.



Cisco has released software updates that address these vulnerabilities.
This advisory is available at the following link:

https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">The following products are affected by the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory:


    Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance 8.6
    Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance 9.0
    Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance 9.1
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">No other Cisco products are currently known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance, formerly known as Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation (HCM), is a service that allows Cisco partners to provide a wide range of Cisco collaboration applications to their customers as a subscriber-based solution.



Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance contains multiple  vulnerabilities that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send a TCP connection flood to disrupt services and cause a DoS condition on the affected system.



Memory Leak Vulnerability



Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance contains a memory leak vulnerability that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker  to execute a sustained flood against vulnerable TCP ports to cause a DoS condition on the affected system.  This vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCub59158["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCub59158"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure (CVE) ID CVE-2013-3390.A system restart is required to clear the condition. Cisco  Hosted Collaboration Mediation Service Assurance 9.1 and earlier are affected.




Memory Exhaustion Vulnerabilities




Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance contains two memory exhaustion vulnerabilities that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker  to execute a sustained TCP connection flood against an affected system. A sustained TCP connection flood against the affected ports will result in memory exhaustion, preventing access to the web GUI  and cause out-of-memory exceptions when executing basic commands.



The first vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCtz90114["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCtz90114"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned CVE ID CVE-2013-3389. TCP ports 61615 and 61616 are affected by this vulnerability. Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Service Assurance 9.1 and earlier is affected.



The second vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCtz92776["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCtz92776"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned CVE ID CVE-2013-3388. The Ephemeral Java Port (44444) is affected by this vulnerability.  Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Service Assurance 9.1 and earlier are affected.



Disk Exhaustion Vulnerability



Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance contains a disk exhaustion vulnerability that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a DoS condition on an affected system. This vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCua42724["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCua42724"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned CVE ID CVE-2013-3387.  A TCP connection flood will generate error logs until the server disk space is exhausted.  The log files must be removed to recover from this condition. The Omnibus Port (TCP 5400) is affected by this vulnerability. Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Service Assurance 9.1 and earlier are affected.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">No workarounds are available for these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">When considering software upgrades, customers are advised to consult the Cisco Security Advisories, Responses, and Notices archive at http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt["http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"] and review subsequent advisories to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution. 






    
        
            Cisco Prime Central for HCS Assurance Version 
             Recommended Release

            
        
        
             8.x
             9.2(1)
        
        
             9.x
             9.2(1)
        
    

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and  confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers. 
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy[https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory. 

These vulnerabilities were discovered through internal testing.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="9">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A stand-alone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy, and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end-users of Cisco products.
</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Name="Cisco" Type="Vendor">
      <Branch Name="Cisco Hosted Collaboration Solution" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-188690">Cisco Hosted Collaboration Solution </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance TCP Flood on Omnibus Port Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCua42724</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCua42724</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2013-3387</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-188690</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.8</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>6.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>No workarounds are available for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance  TCP Flood on Prime Central Ephemeral Java Port Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCtz92776</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCtz92776</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2013-3388</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-188690</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.8</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>6.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>No workarounds are available for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="3" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance TCP Flood on ActiveMQ Broker Ports Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCtz90114</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCtz90114</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2013-3389</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-188690</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.8</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>6.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>No workarounds are available for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="4" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance TCP Flood on Impact Ephemeral Ports Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCub59158</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCub59158</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2013-3390</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-188690</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.8</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>6.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>No workarounds are available for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20130821-hcm</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Prime Central for Hosted Collaboration Solution Assurance Denial of Service Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
