<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Controller Vulnerabilities</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-iosxr-ponctlr-ci-OHcHmsFL</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.0</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2024-09-11T15:46:32</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2024-09-11T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2024-09-11T16:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
      <cvrf:Date>2024-09-11T15:47:05.1618459Z</cvrf:Date>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network (PON) Controller Software, which runs as a docker container on hardware that is supported by Cisco IOS XR Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform command injection attacks, execute arbitrary commands on the affected system, or retrieve a cleartext password.

For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address these vulnerabilities. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-iosxr-ponctlr-ci-OHcHmsFL ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-iosxr-ponctlr-ci-OHcHmsFL"]

This advisory is part of the September 2024 release of the Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication. For a complete list of the advisories and links to them, see Cisco Event Response: September 2024 Semiannual Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewErp.x?alertId=ERP-75416"].</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">These vulnerabilities affect the following Cisco hardware platforms if they are running a vulnerable release of Cisco IOS XR Software and are configured with the Routed PON Controller feature:

Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers

NCS 540-24Q8L2DD-SYS Router
NCS 540-24Z8Q2C-SYS Router
NCS 540-28Z4C-SYS-A Router
NCS 540-28Z4C-SYS-D Router
NCS 540-ACC-SYS Router
NCS 540X-16Z4G8Q2C-A Router
NCS 540X-16Z4G8Q2C-D Router

NCS 5500 Series

NCS 55A1-24Q6H-SS
NCS 55A2-MOD-SE-S

NCS 5700 Series

NCS-57C1-48Q6-SYS
NCS 57C3-MOD

For information about which Cisco software releases are vulnerable, see the Fixed Software ["#fs"] section of this advisory.

For information about the Cisco PON Controller solution, see the Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Deployment Guide. ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/iosxr/pon/guides/b-cisco-pon-solution.html"]

Determine Whether PON Controller Software is Enabled

To determine whether Cisco IOS XR Software has the PON Controller enabled, use the show running-config pon-ctlr command on the CLI of an affected device. The device is affected by these vulnerabilities if the command returns output indicating that the PON Controller is configured on a device, as shown in the following example:


RP/0/RP0/CPU0:Router#show running-config pon-ctrl
Wed Sep 11 03:00:53.842 UTC
pon-ctlr
 cfg-file harddisk:/PonCntlInit.json vrf default
RP/0/RP0/CPU0:Router#
.
.
.

If the output is empty or the command does not exist, the device is not affected by these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.

Cisco has confirmed that these vulnerabilities do not affect the following Cisco products:

IOS Software
IOS XE Software
NX-OS Software</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">The vulnerabilities are not dependent on one another. Exploitation of one of the vulnerabilities is not required to exploit another vulnerability. In addition, a software release that is affected by one of the vulnerabilities may not be affected by the other vulnerabilities.

Details about the vulnerabilities are as follows:

CVE-2024-20483: Cisco Routed PON Controller Command Injection Vulnerabilities

Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Routed PON Controller Software, which runs as a docker container on hardware that is supported by Cisco IOS XR Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges on the PON Manager or direct access to the PON Manager MongoDB instance to perform command injection attacks on the PON Controller container and execute arbitrary commands as root.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the PON controller.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address these vulnerabilities. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

Bug ID(s): CSCwi81012 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwi81012"], CSCwi81013 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwi81013"]
CVE ID: CVE-2024-20483
Security Impact Rating (SIR): High
CVSS Base Score: 7.2
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H

CVE-2024-20489: Cisco Routed PON Controller Cleartext Password Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the storage method of the PON Controller configuration file could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to obtain the MongoDB credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper storage of the unencrypted database credentials on the device that is running Cisco IOS XR Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the configuration files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view MongoDB credentials.

Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwi81017 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwi81017"]
CVE ID: CVE-2024-20489
Security Impact Rating (SIR): High
CVSS Base Score: 8.4
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:N</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators may choose to restrict MongoDB access to IP addresses of the PON Manager and each Cisco IOS XR Software PON Controller. For help with implementing these restrictions, refer to the MongoDB documentation.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">Cisco plans to release software updates that address vulnerabilities described in this advisory. Customers with service contracts that entitle them to regular software updates should obtain security fixes through their usual update channels.

Customers may only install and expect support for software versions and feature sets for which they have purchased a license. By installing, downloading, accessing, or otherwise using such software upgrades, customers agree to follow the terms of the Cisco software license:
https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/end-user-license-agreement.html ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/end-user-license-agreement.html"]

Additionally, customers may only download software for which they have a valid license, procured from Cisco directly, or through a Cisco authorized reseller or partner. In most cases this will be a maintenance upgrade to software that was previously purchased. Free security software updates do not entitle customers to a new software license, additional software feature sets, or major revision upgrades.

The Cisco Support and Downloads page ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/index.html"] on Cisco.com provides information about licensing and downloads. This page can also display customer device support coverage for customers who use the My Devices tool.

When considering software upgrades ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.
  Customers Without Service Contracts
Customers who purchase directly from Cisco but do not hold a Cisco service contract and customers who make purchases through third-party vendors but are unsuccessful in obtaining fixed software through their point of sale should obtain upgrades by contacting the Cisco TAC: https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/web/tsd-cisco-worldwide-contacts.html ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/web/tsd-cisco-worldwide-contacts.html"]

Customers should have the product serial number available and be prepared to provide the URL of this advisory as evidence of entitlement to a free upgrade.
      Fixed Releases
In the following table, the left column lists Cisco software releases or trains. The right column indicates whether a release (train) is affected by the vulnerability that is described in this advisory and the first release that includes the fix for this vulnerability.
        Cisco Routed PON Controller Software in Cisco IOS XR1  First Fixed Release          7.11 and earlier  Not vulnerable.      24.1 and later  Migrate to a fixed release.      24.2 and later  Migrate to a fixed release.      24.3 and later  Migrate to a fixed release.      24.4.1 (Nov 2024)  Not vulnerable.
1. Cisco Routed PON Controller Software is bundled with Cisco IOS XR Software as an optional RPM Package Manager.

The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) validates only the affected and fixed release information that is documented in this advisory.

After upgrading to fixed software, a configuration change is required in the PonCntlInit.json file to use a keyring to store the MongoDB password.

Instructions for PonCntlInit.json Configuration Change

After upgrading to fixed software, replace the MongoDB password field in the PonCntlInit.json file with the password_opts field, as shown in the following example.

Before the configuration change, the MongoDB password field will appear as shown in the following example:


"MongoDB": {
        "auth_db": "tibit_users",
.
.
.
.
      "password": "MongoDBPassword",
.
.
}

After upgrading to fixed software, replace the MongoDB password field with the password_opts field, as shown in the following example:



"MongoDB": {
.
.
.
"password_opts": {
"type": "keyring",
"keyring_path": "/etc/cisco/poncntl/keyring.data",
"keyring_key_path": "/etc/cisco/poncntl/keyring.key"
},
.
.
}

Once the PonCntlInit.json file has been edited, update the Cisco IOS XR Software configuration to include the database password. Once the configuration is saved, the password will be shown in encrypted format when the show running-config command is performed, as shown in the following example:


Router#conf t
Wed Sep 11 16:00:00.000 UTC
Router(config)#pon-ctlr
Router(config-ponctlr)#cfg-file /harddisk:/PonCntlInit.json db-password &lt;MongoDB Password&gt;
Router(config-ponctlr)#end
RP/0/RP0/CPU0:Sep 11 16:00:00.000 UTC: config[67636]: %MGBL-SYS-5-CONFIG_I : Configured from console by admin
Router#show running-config pon-ctlr
Wed Sep 11 16:00:00.000 UTC
pon-ctlr
 cfg-file /harddisk:/PonCntlInit.json db-password 0525253C1E6E6925
!
Router#</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco PSIRT is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">These vulnerabilities were found during internal security testing by James Spadaro of the Cisco Advanced Security Initiatives Group (ASIG).</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-iosxr-ponctlr-ci-OHcHmsFL</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Controller Vulnerabilities</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
    <cvrf:Reference>
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewErp.x?alertId=ERP-75416</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Event Response: September 2024 Semiannual Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco IOS XR Software">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-5834">Cisco IOS XR Software </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco IOS XR PON Controller Command Injection Vulnerabilities</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwi81012</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwi81012,CSCwi81013</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2024-20483</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-5834</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>7.2</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators may choose to restrict MongoDB access to IP addresses of the PON Manager and each Cisco IOS XR Software PON Controller. For help with implementing these restrictions, refer to the MongoDB documentation.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-iosxr-ponctlr-ci-OHcHmsFL</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Controller Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Cleartext Password Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwi81017</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwi81017</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2024-20489</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-5834</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>8.4</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities. However, administrators may choose to restrict MongoDB access to IP addresses of the PON Manager and each Cisco IOS XR Software PON Controller. For help with implementing these restrictions, refer to the MongoDB documentation.

While this mitigation has been deployed and was proven successful in a test environment, customers should determine the applicability and effectiveness in their own environment and under their own use conditions. Customers should be aware that any workaround or mitigation that is implemented may negatively impact the functionality or performance of their network based on intrinsic customer deployment scenarios and limitations. Customers should not deploy any workarounds or mitigations before first evaluating the applicability to their own environment and any impact to such environment.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-iosxr-ponctlr-ci-OHcHmsFL</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Controller Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
