<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server Vulnerabilities</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.2</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-05-18T15:42:51</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2022-05-24T20:09:16</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated note to indicate CVE-2022-20809 only affects Cisco products that have debug logging enabled.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.2</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2023-01-17T20:24:01</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated CVE IDs in the note.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2022-05-18T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2023-01-17T20:24:01</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Multiple vulnerabilities in the API and web-based management interfaces of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to write files or disclose sensitive information on an affected device.

For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.

Cisco has released software updates that address these vulnerabilities. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">At the time of publication, these vulnerabilities affected Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS.

Note: The default configuration is vulnerable for CVE-2022-20806 and CVE-2022-20807. CVE-2022-20809 only affects Cisco products that have debug logging enabled.

For information about which Cisco software releases were vulnerable at the time of publication, see the Fixed Software ["#fs"] section of this advisory. See the Details section in the bug ID(s) at the top of this advisory for the most complete and current information.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">The vulnerabilities are not dependent on one another. Exploitation of one of the vulnerabilities is not required to exploit another vulnerability. In addition, a software release that is affected by one of the vulnerabilities may not be affected by the other vulnerabilities.

Details about the vulnerabilities are as follows:

CVE-2022-20806: Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the cluster database API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read/write privileges on the application to obtain sensitive information and cause a partial denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user-supplied command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device with read/write privileges and issuing a crafted command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system at a rate that impacts system performance.

Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCvz71486 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCvz71486"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20806
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Medium
CVSS Base Score: 5.5
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:L

CVE-2022-20807: Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS XML External Entity Injection Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the file-parsing logic of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read/write privileges to obtain sensitive information on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted XML file that contains references to external entities. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files from the local system, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive information on an affected system.

Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwa25061 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwa25061"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20807
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Medium
CVSS Base Score: 4.9
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N

CVE-2022-20809: Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability

A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information in clear text on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to the storage of unencrypted credentials in certain logs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the logs on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view the credentials of other users of the shared device. This vulnerability only occurs when debug logging is enabled on the device.

Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

Bug ID(s): CSCwa25106 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwa25106"]
CVE ID: CVE-2022-20809
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Medium
CVSS Base Score: 4.3
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">When considering software upgrades ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.
      Fixed Releases
At the time of publication, the release information in the following table(s) was accurate. See the Details section in the bug ID(s) at the top of this advisory for the most complete and current information.

The left column lists Cisco software releases, and the right column indicates whether a release was affected by the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory and which release included the fix for these vulnerabilities.
        Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS Release  First Fixed Release          Earlier than 14.0  Migrate to a fixed release.      14.0  14.0.7
The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) validates only the affected and fixed release information that is documented in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco PSIRT is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerability that is described in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">These vulnerabilities were found during internal security testing by Jason Crowder of the Cisco Advanced Security Initiatives Group (ASIG).</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server Vulnerabilities</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-209614">Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwa25106</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwa25106</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20809</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209614</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>4.3</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCvz71486</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCvz71486</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20806</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209614</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>5.5</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:L</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="3" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence VCS XML External Entity Injection Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwa25061</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwa25061</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2022-20807</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-209614</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>4.9</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-expressway-filewrite-bsFVwueV</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
