<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server and Cisco Expressway Software</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-20141015-vcs</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.0</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2014-10-15T14:13:52</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2014-10-15T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2014-10-15T16:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) and Cisco Expressway Software includes the following vulnerabilities:


    Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway Crafted Packets Denial of Service Vulnerability
    Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP IX Filter Denial of Service Vulnerability
    Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability 

Succesfull exploitation of any of these vulnerabilities could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a reload of the affected system, which may result in a Denial of Service (DoS) condition.



Cisco has released software updates that address these vulnerabilities. Workarounds that mitigate these vulnerabilities are not available. This advisory is available at the following link:

https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20141015-vcs["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20141015-vcs"]



Note: This security advisory does not provide information about
the GNU Bash Environment Variable Command Injection Vulnerability (also known as Shellshock).
For additional information regarding Cisco products affected by this
vulnerability, refer to the Cisco Security Advisory at the following
link: https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20140926-bash["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20140926-bash"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">These vulnerabilities apply to the following products running an affected version of software:


    Cisco TelePresence VCS Control
    Cisco
    TelePresence VCS Expressway
    Cisco TelePresence VCS Starter Pack
    Expressway
    Cisco Expressway Core
    Cisco Expressway Edge 

Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway hardware and virtual appliances are both affected by these vulnerabilities.



The Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway Crafted Packets Denial of Service Vulnerability and Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability affect Cisco TelePresence VCS or Cisco Expressway in default configuration.



The Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP IX Filter Denial of Service Vulnerability affects the Cisco TelePresence VCS or Cisco Expressway if IX filter is configured. To determine whether the IX filter is configured, use the xconfig zone zone command and verify that xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP UDP IX Filter Mode parameter is set to On. The following example shows a Cisco TelePresence VCS or Cisco Expressway with the IX filter enabled:




[...]
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP SearchAutoResponse: "Off"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP TLS Verify Mode: "Off"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP Transport: "TCP"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP UDP BFCP Filter Mode: "Off"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP UDP IX Filter Mode: "On"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SIP UPDATE Strip Mode: "Off"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor SignalingRouting Mode: "Auto"
*c xConfiguration Zones Zone 2 Neighbor ZoneProfile: "CiscoUnifiedCommunicationsManagerBFCP"
[...] 
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">No other Cisco products are currently known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">Cisco TelePresence VCS
extends the benefits of face-to-face video collaboration across networks
and organizations by supporting any-to-any video and telepresence
communications.  Cisco Expressway is designed specifically for comprehensive
collaboration services provided through Cisco Unified Communications
Manager, Cisco Business Edition, or Cisco Hosted Collaboration Solution. It features established firewall-traversal technology and helps
redefine traditional enterprise collaboration boundaries.



Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway Crafted Packets Denial of Service Vulnerability



A vulnerability in the packets processing function  could allow an
unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a kernel crash and the reload of the affected
system.



The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of
crafted packets when processed by the system. An attacker
could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IP packets to the
affected system at a high rate.



This vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCui06507["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCui06507"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned Common Vulnerability and Exposures (CVE) ID  CVE-2014-3368



Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP IX Filter Denial of Service Vulnerability



A vulnerability in the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP)
IX Channel feature code  could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker
to cause the reload of the affected system.


The vulnerability is
due to improper handling of crafted Session Description Protocol (SDP) packets when the IX filter is
configured. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending
crafted SDP packets to the affected system. 



This vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCuo42252["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCuo42252"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned CVE ID CVE-2014-3369



Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability



A vulnerability in Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) module  could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the reload of the affected system.



The
vulnerability is due to improper handling of crafted SIP packets. An
attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SIP packets
to the affected system



This vulnerability is documented in Cisco bug ID CSCum60447["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCum60447"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and CSCum60442["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCum60442"] (registered["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only) and has been assigned CVE ID CVE-2014-3370</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There are no workarounds for these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">When considering software upgrades, customers are advised to consult the Cisco Security Advisories, Responses, and Notices archive at http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt["http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"] and review subsequent advisories to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution. 

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and  confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers. 



The following table summarizes the first fixed release for each
vulnerability in both Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway software. The Recommended Release row gives
information on the recommended release that resolves all the
vulnerabilities in this security advisory.




    
        
             
             First Fixed Release

            
            
        
        
            Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway Crafted Packets Denial of Service Vulnerability

            
            X8.2 and later

            
        
        
            Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP IX Filter Denial of Service Vulnerability

            
            X8.1.1 and later

            
        
        
            Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability

            
            X8.1.1 and later

            
        
        
             Recommended Release

            
            
             X8.2 and later

            
        
    



Note: This security advisory does not provide information about
the GNU Bash Environment Variable Command Injection Vulnerability (also known as Shellshock). Customer should refer to the Cisco Security Advisory at the following
link: https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20140926-bash["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20140926-bash"] before making decisions about the Cisco TelePresence VCS or Cisco Expressway software version.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy[https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerabilities that are described in this advisory. 

These vulnerabilities were found during internal tests.
</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="9">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A stand-alone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy, and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end-users of Cisco products.
</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20141015-vcs</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server and Cisco Expressway Software</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
    <cvrf:Reference>
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewAlert.x?alertId=35827</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway Crafted Packets Denial of Service Vulnerability</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
    <cvrf:Reference>
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewAlert.x?alertId=35828</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP IX Filter Denial of Service Vulnerability</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
    <cvrf:Reference>
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/viewAlert.x?alertId=35829</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Name="Cisco" Type="Vendor">
      <Branch Name="Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS)" Type="Product Name">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-112250">Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway Crafted Packets Denial of Service Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCui06507</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCui06507</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2014-3368</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-112250</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.8</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>6.4</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:L/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20141015-vcs</URL>
        <Description>Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server and Cisco Expressway Software</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP IX Filter Denial of Service Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCuo42252</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCuo42252</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2014-3369</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-112250</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.1</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>5.9</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:M/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20141015-vcs</URL>
        <Description>Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server and Cisco Expressway Software</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="3" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco TelePresence VCS and Cisco Expressway SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCum60447</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCum60447,CSCum60442</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2014-3370</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-112250</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV2>
        <BaseScoreV2>7.1</BaseScoreV2>
        <TemporalScoreV2>5.9</TemporalScoreV2>
        <VectorV2>AV:N/AC:M/Au:N/C:N/I:N/A:C/E:F/RL:OF/RC:C</VectorV2>
      </ScoreSetV2>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds for these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20141015-vcs</URL>
        <Description>Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server and Cisco Expressway Software</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
