<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Integrated Management Controller Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-ucs-kvmsxss-6h7AnUyk</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>1.0</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-08-27T15:57:38</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2025-08-27T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2025-08-27T16:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
      <cvrf:Date>2025-08-27T15:58:09.8731312Z</cvrf:Date>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">A vulnerability in the Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor (vKVM) connection handling of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid user credentials with privileges that allow for vKVM access on the affected device.

Note: The affected vKVM client is also included in Cisco UCS Manager.

Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ucs-kvmsxss-6h7AnUyk ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ucs-kvmsxss-6h7AnUyk"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">At the time of publication, this vulnerability affected the following Cisco products if they were running a vulnerable software release, regardless of device configuration:

Catalyst 8300 Series Edge uCPE (CSCwo77420 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwo77420"])
Cisco UCS Manager Software (CSCwq34766 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwq34766"])
UCS B-Series Blade Servers (CSCwm57433 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwm57433"])
UCS C-Series M6, M7, and M8 Rack Servers (CSCwn43958 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwn43958"])
UCS E-Series Servers M6 (CSCwo77420 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwo77420"])
UCS X-Series Modular System (CSCwm57433 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwm57433"])

Cisco appliances that are based on a preconfigured version of one of the Cisco UCS C-Series Servers that are in the preceding list were also affected by this vulnerability if they exposed access to the Cisco IMC UI. At the time of publication, this included the following Cisco products:

Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) Servers
Business Edition 6000 and 7000 Appliances
Catalyst Center Appliances, formerly DNA Center
Cisco Telemetry Broker Appliance
Cloud Services Platform (CSP) 5000 Series
Common Services Platform Collector (CSPC) Appliances
Connected Mobile Experiences (CMX) Appliances
Connected Safety and Security UCS Platform Series Servers
Cyber Vision Center Appliances
Expressway Series Appliances
HyperFlex Edge Nodes
HyperFlex Nodes
IEC6400 Edge Compute Appliances
IOS XRv 9000 Appliances
Meeting Server 1000 Appliances
Nexus Dashboard Appliances
Prime Infrastructure Appliances
Prime Network Registrar Jumpstart Appliances
Secure Endpoint Private Cloud Appliances
Secure Firewall Management Center Appliances
Secure Malware Analytics Appliances
Secure Network Analytics Appliances
Secure Network Server Appliances
Secure Workload Servers

For information about which Cisco software releases were vulnerable at the time of publication, see the Fixed Software ["#fs"] section of this advisory. See the Details section in the bug IDs at the top of this advisory for the most complete and current information.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by this vulnerability.

Cisco has confirmed that this vulnerability does not affect the following Cisco products:

5000 Series Enterprise Network Compute Systems (ENCS)
UCS C-Series M5
UCS E-Series Servers M3
UCS S-Series Storage Servers</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="4">There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="5">When considering software upgrades ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.
      Fixed Releases
At the time of publication, the release information in the following tables was accurate. See the Details section in the bug ID(s) at the top of this advisory for the most complete and current information.

The left column lists Cisco software releases, and the right column indicates whether a release was affected by the vulnerability that is described in this advisory and which release included the fix for this vulnerability.

Catalyst 8300 Series Edge uCPE

Note: Cisco IMC on Cisco Catalyst 8300 Series Edge uCPE is included in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS). Cisco IMC is upgraded as part of the firmware auto-upgrade process in NFVIS.
        Cisco NFVIS Release  First Fixed Release          4.18 and earlier  4.18.1
UCS Manager Software
        Cisco UCS Manager Software Release  First Fixed Release          4.1 and earlier  Migrate to a fixed release.      4.2  4.2(3p)      4.3  4.3(6a)      6.0  Not vulnerable.
UCS B-Series and X-Series Servers in UCS Manager Mode
        Cisco UCS Server Software Release  First Fixed Release          4.1 and earlier  Migrate to a fixed release.      4.2  4.2(3o)      4.3  4.3(5c)      6.0  Not vulnerable.
UCS B-Series Servers in Intersight Managed Mode
        Cisco Intersight Server Firmware Release  First Fixed Release          Earlier than 4.2  Migrate to a fixed release.      4.2  4.2(3l)      5.1  Migrate to a fixed release.      5.2  Migrate to a fixed release.      5.3  5.3(0.250001)      5.4  Not vulnerable.      6.0  Not vulnerable.
UCS X-Series Servers in Intersight Managed Mode
        Cisco Intersight Server Firmware Release  First Fixed Release          5.0  5.0(4i)      5.1  Migrate to a fixed release.      5.2  Migrate to a fixed release.      5.3  5.3(0.250001)      5.4  Not vulnerable.      6.0  Not vulnerable.
UCS C-Series Servers in Standalone Mode or Intersight Managed Mode

        Cisco UCS Server Software Release  First Fixed Release          Earlier than 4.2  Migrate to a fixed release.      4.2  4.2(3o)      4.3  4.3(5.250001)      6.0  Not vulnerable.
UCS C-Series Servers in UCS Manager Mode

        Cisco UCS Server Software Release  First Fixed Release          Earlier than 4.2  Migrate to a fixed release.      4.2  4.2(3o)      4.3  4.3(5c)      6.0  Not vulnerable.
UCS E-Series M6 Server
        Cisco UCS Server Software Release  First Fixed Release          4.15 and earlier  4.15.2
Note: For Cisco appliances that are based on a preconfigured version of a Cisco UCS C-Series Server, administrators can perform a direct upgrade of the Cisco IMC software to one of the fixed releases as indicated in the preceding tables. For instructions, see the Cisco Host Upgrade Utility User Guide ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/unified_computing/ucs/c/sw/lomug/4-2/b_cisco-host-upgrade-utility-user-guide-4-2/m_upgrading-the-firmware.html"]. The exceptions are the appliances that are listed in the following table. For these appliances, follow the instructions in the Remediation column:
        Cisco Hardware Platform  First Fixed Cisco IMC Release  Remediation          Cisco Telemetry Broker Appliance  4.3(5.250030)  Apply the firmware update m6-tb2300-ctb-firmware-4.3-5.250030.iso ["https://www.cisco.com/c/dam/en/us/td/docs/security/Telemetry_Broker/Release-Notes/m6-tb2300-ctb-firmware-4_3-5_250030_iso_DV_1_0.pdf"].      IEC6400 Edge Compute Appliances  4.3(5.250033)  Apply the HUU upgrade using IEC6400-HUU-4.3.5.img.      Secure Endpoint Private Cloud Appliances  4.3(6.250053)  Upgrade to version 4.2.5 or later and then follow the steps documented in the TechNote ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/docs/security/secure-endpoint-private-cloud/222008-cisco-secure-endpoint-private-cloud-firm.html"].      Secure Firewall Management Center Appliances  4.3(6.250053)  Apply Hotfix l ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/secure-firewall/release-notes/threat-defense/hotfix/threat-defense-release-notes-hotfix.html#Cisco_Reference.dita_e5a104de-579f-48b7-adb6-0a72dc5183b7"].      Secure Malware Analytics Appliances  4.3(6.250053)  Update the firmware using the Out-of-Band Firmware Update ISO ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/secure-malware-analytics/admin-guide/v2-19/secure-malware-analytics-guide/m_oob-update-firmware.html"] procedure.      Secure Network Analytics Appliances  4.3(5.250030)  Install update patch-common-SNA-FIRMWARE-20250403-v2-01.swu ["https://www.cisco.com/c/dam/en/us/td/docs/security/stealthwatch/cimc_bios/7_5_3_M6_CIMC_firmware_4_3_5_250030_readme_DV_1_0.pdf"].      Secure Network Server Appliances  4.3(5.250001)  Apply the BIOS and HUU upgrade as documented in the Firmware Upgrade Guide for Cisco SNS 3700 Series ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/ise/sns3700hig/sns-37xx-firmware-4-x-xx_upgrade_guide.html#r_overview"].
The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) validates only the affected and fixed release information that is documented in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="6">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="7">The Cisco PSIRT is not aware of any public announcements or malicious use of the vulnerability that is described in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="8">This vulnerability was found during internal security testing.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="9">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ucs-kvmsxss-6h7AnUyk</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Integrated Management Controller Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-112776">Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed) </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Unified Computing System (Standalone)">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-191638">Cisco Unified Computing System (Standalone) </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Unified Computing System E-Series Software (UCSE)">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-201970">Cisco Unified Computing System E-Series Software (UCSE) </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Integrated Management Controller Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor (vKVM) Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwm57433</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwm57433,CSCwq34766,CSCwn43958,CSCwo77420</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2025-20342</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-112776</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-191638</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-201970</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>5.4</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ucs-kvmsxss-6h7AnUyk</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Integrated Management Controller Virtual Keyboard Video Monitor Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
