<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>SIP Packets Reload IOS Devices with support for SIP</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-20070131-sip</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>2.1</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2011-10-06T12:19:01</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Added Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) scoring for all
            bugs mentioned in the advisory. 
             Added
            CSCsh58082
            (
            registered customers only)
            as the Cisco Bug ID that tracks the root
            cause of the vulnerability. 
             Minor wording changes.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>2.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2007-01-31T00:00:00</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Changed formatting and wording of advisory table.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2007-01-31T00:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2007-01-31T00:00:00</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Cisco devices running an affected version of Internetwork Operating  System (IOS) which supports Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) are affected by a  vulnerability that may lead to a reload of the device when receiving a specific  series of packets destined to port 5060. This issue is compounded by a related  bug which allows traffic to TCP 5060 and UDP port 5060 on devices not  configured for SIP.

There are no known instances of intentional exploitation of this issue.  However, Cisco has observed data streams that appear to be unintentionally  triggering the vulnerability.

Workarounds exist to mitigate the effects of this problem on devices  which do not require SIP.
  This advisory is posted at https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20070131-sip ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20070131-sip"].</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">Any Cisco device which runs a vulnerable version of IOS and supports  SIP processing could be vulnerable. This includes IOS versions 12.3(4)XH,  12.3(4)XQ, 12.3(7)XR, 12.3(7)XS, 12.3(8)JA, 12.3(8)T, 12.3(8)XU, 12.3(8)XW,  12.3(8)XX, 12.3(8)XY, 12.3(8)YA, 12.3(8)YG, 12.3(8)YH, 12.3(8)YI, 12.3(8)ZA,  12.4 Mainline and 12.4T onward. Routers configured as SIP Public Switched  Telephone Network (PSTN) Gateways are vulnerable, as are routers configured as  SIP Session Border Controllers (SBCs) and the CAT6000-CMM card.

To determine if your device has SIP enabled, enter the commands  show ip sockets and show tcp brief  all. Below is an example of a router running code without the  fix, and without the workaround enabled. The router in this example is running  the vulnerable image c7200-p-mz.124-3.bin:


Router#show ip sockets
Proto    Remote      Port      Local       Port  In Out Stat TTY OutputIF  17 0.0.0.0             0  --any--          5060   0   0  211   0  17 0.0.0.0             0 192.168.100.2       67   0   0 2211   0  17 0.0.0.0             0 192.168.100.2     2517   0   0   11   0

The first line with UDP Port 5060 shows that UDP SIP is enabled.


Router#show tcp brief all
TCB       Local Address           Foreign Address        (state)  2051E680  *.5060                  *.*                    LISTEN

The above lines with *.5060 show that TCP SIP is enabled.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Devices that do not support SIP processing are not affected by this  issue. This includes but is not limited to the 6500, 7600, 10000 series and  12000 series. To confirm that a device is not vulnerable to this issue, ensure  that ports TCP 5060 and UDP 5060 are not open on the device with the commands  show tcp brief all and show ip  sockets. Below is an example of a router running the fixed image  c7200-js-mz.124-5b.bin which is not vulnerable to this issue.


Router#show tcp brief all
  Router#show ip sockets  Proto    Remote      Port      Local       Port  In Out Stat TTY OutputIF  17 0.0.0.0             0 192.168.100.2      67   0   0 2211   0

No lines with UDP Port 5060 are shown and UDP SIP is not enabled. In  this example, UDP port 67 is used by DHCP which is not related to this  vulnerability.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">SIP is a protocol designed for use in IP voice networks and is widely  used for Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) communications worldwide.

Cisco devices running certain versions of IOS with support for SIP  services may be affected by a vulnerability that leads to a reload of the  device with a crafted series of SIP packets to either TCP port 5060 or UDP port  5060. This vulnerability affects routers that contain any SIP configuration,  including SIP gateways. This issue is being tracked as Cisco Bug ID  CSCsh58082 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCsh58082"]  (  registered ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only)  .

In addition, certain versions of IOS with support for SIP services may  process SIP messages even if they are not configured for SIP operation. To  process SIP messages IOS will open UDP port 5060 and TCP port 5060 for  listening. The Cisco Bug ID that documents the issue of IOS processing SIP  messages without being configured for SIP operation is  CSCsb25337 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCsb25337"]  (  registered ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only)  . The fix for this bug turns off the  listening ports TCP 5060 and UDP 5060.

A device must have an open SIP port to be vulnerable to this issue.  Devices which do not listen on TCP 5060 or UDP 5060 are not vulnerable. Because  SIP utilizes UDP as a transport, it is possible to spoof the sender's IP  address, which may defeat ACLs that permit communication to these ports from  trusted IP addresses.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">Additional mitigations that can be deployed on Cisco devices within the  network are available in the Cisco Applied Mitigation Bulletin companion  document for this advisory:  https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoAppliedMitigationBulletin/cisco-amb-20070131-sip ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoAppliedMitigationBulletin/cisco-amb-20070131-sip"].
  Disable SIP listening ports
For devices which do not require SIP to be enabled, the simplest and  most effective workaround is to disable SIP processing on the device with the  following commands.

  Warning: When applying this workaround to devices  which are processing MGCP or H.323 calls, the device will not allow you to stop  SIP processing while active calls are being processed. Under these  circumstances, this workaround should be implemented during a maintenance  window when active calls can be briefly stopped.


Enter configuration commands, one per line.  End with CNTL/Z.
Router(config)#sip-ua  Router(config-sip-ua)#no transport udp  Router(config-sip-ua)#no transport tcp  Router(config-sip-ua)#end

After applying this workaround the commands show ip  sockets and show tcp brief all will  not show the device listening on UDP and TCP port 5060:


Router#show ip sockets
Proto    Remote      Port      Local       Port  In Out Stat TTY   17   --listen--          9.13.32.18       2887   0   0   11   0    Router#show tcp brief all  TCB       Local Address           Foreign Address        (state)  6649A5A4  *.1720                  *.*                    LISTEN  66CDC764  *.1723                  *.*                    LISTEN
    Control Plane Policing
For devices which do not need to run SIP, you can use Control Plane  Policing (CoPP) to block all SIP access to the device. Cisco IOS software  releases 12.0S, 12.2SX, 12.2S, 12.3T, 12.4, and 12.4T support the CoPP feature.  CoPP may be configured on a device to protect the management and control planes  to minimize the risk and effectiveness of direct infrastructure attacks by  explicitly permitting only authorized traffic sent to infrastructure devices in  accordance with existing security policies and configurations. The following  example can be adapted to your network.

  Warning: Because SIP utilizes UDP as a transport, it  is possible to spoof the sender's IP address, which may defeat ACLs that permit  communication to these ports from trusted IP addresses.



!-- Permit all TCP and UDP SIP traffic sent to all IP addresses  !-- configured on all interfaces of the affected device so that it  !-- will be policed and dropped by the CoPP feature.      access-list 100 permit tcp any any eq 5060  access-list 100 permit udp any any eq 5060      !-- Permit (Police or Drop)/Deny (Allow) all other Layer3 and Layer4  !-- traffic in accordance with existing security policies and  !-- configurations for traffic that is authorized to be sent  !-- to infrastructure devices.        !-- Create a Class-Map for traffic to be policed by  !-- the CoPP feature.      class-map match-all drop-sip-class    match access-group 100      !-- Create a Policy-Map that will be applied to the  !-- Control-Plane of the device.      policy-map drop-sip-traffic    class drop-sip-class      drop      !-- Apply the Policy-Map to the Control-Plane of the  !-- device.      control-plane    service-policy input drop-sip-traffic

In the above CoPP example, the access control list entries (ACEs) which  match the potential exploit packets with the "permit" action result in these  packets being discarded by the policy-map "drop" function, while packets that  match the "deny" action (not shown) are not affected by the policy-map drop  function. Additional information on the configuration and use of the CoPP  feature can be found at  http://www.cisco.com/en/US/prod/collateral/iosswrel/ps6537/ps6586/ps6642/prod_white_paper0900aecd804fa16a.html ["http://www.cisco.com/en/US/prod/collateral/iosswrel/ps6537/ps6586/ps6642/prod_white_paper0900aecd804fa16a.html"]  and  http://www.cisco.com/en/US/docs/ios/12_3t/12_3t4/feature/guide/gtrtlimt.html ["http://www.cisco.com/en/US/docs/ios/12_3t/12_3t4/feature/guide/gtrtlimt.html"].</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">When considering software upgrades, also consult  http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt ["http://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"]  and any subsequent advisories to determine exposure and a complete upgrade  solution.

 In all cases, customers should exercise caution to be certain the  devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and that current hardware and  software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new  release. If the information is not clear, contact the Cisco Technical  Assistance Center ("TAC") or your contracted maintenance provider for  assistance.

 Each row of the Cisco IOS software table (below) describes a release  train and the platforms or products for which it is intended. If a given  release train is vulnerable, then the earliest possible releases that contain  the fix (the "First Fixed Release") and the anticipated date of availability  for each are listed in the "Rebuild" and "Maintenance" columns. A device  running a release in the given train that is earlier than the release in a  specific column (less than the First Fixed Release) is known to be vulnerable.  The release should be upgraded at least to the indicated release or a later  version (greater than or equal to the First Fixed Release label).

For more information on the terms "Rebuild" and "Maintenance," consult  the following URL: http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/intelligence/ios-ref.html ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/intelligence/ios-ref.html"].

 The following table is written to indicate the vulnerable and fixed  status of  CSCsh58082 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCsh58082"]  (  registered ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only)  , which is the bug responsible for the  device reload. This table also contains information about IOS releases that are  fixed for  CSCsb25337 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCsb25337"]  (  registered ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only)  , which turns off processing of SIP  messages when the device is not fully configured for SIP operation. At the time  of the 2.0 publishing, there are no fixes for  CSCsh58082 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCsh58082"]  (  registered ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.comRPF/register/register.do"] customers only)  .

Major Release

Availability of Repaired Releases

              Affected 12.0-Based Release

              Rebuild

              Maintenance

12.0

All 12.0 releases are not vulnerable

              Affected 12.1-Based Release

              Rebuild

              Maintenance

12.1

All 12.1 releases are not vulnerable

              Affected 12.2-Based Release

              Rebuild

              Maintenance

12.2

All 12.2 releases are not vulnerable

              Affected 12.3-Based Release

              Rebuild

              Maintenance

12.3

Not vulnerable

12.3B

Not vulnerable

12.3BC

Not vulnerable

12.3BW

Not vulnerable

12.3JA

Not vulnerable

12.3JEA

Not vulnerable

12.3JK

Not vulnerable

12.3JX

Not vulnerable

12.3T

Vulnerable in all 12.3(8)T and later releases

12.3TPC

Not vulnerable

12.3XA

Not vulnerable

12.3XB

Not vulnerable

12.3XC

Not vulnerable

12.3XD

Not vulnerable

12.3XE

Not vulnerable

12.3XF

Not vulnerable

12.3XG

Not vulnerable

12.3XH

Vulnerable

12.3XI

Not vulnerable

12.3XJ

Not vulnerable

12.3XK

Not vulnerable

12.3XQ

Vulnerable

12.3XR

Vulnerable

12.3XS

Not vulnerable

12.3XU

Vulnerable

12.3XW

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.3(14)YX2 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.3XX

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.3(8)XX2 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.3XY

Vulnerable

12.3YA

Not vulnerable

12.3YD

Not vulnerable

12.3YF

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.3(14)YX2 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.3YG

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.3(8)YG5 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.3YH

Not vulnerable

12.3YI

Not vulnerable

12.3YJ

Not vulnerable

12.3YK

Vulnerable

12.3YM

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.3(14)YM8 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.3YQ

Vulnerable

12.3YS

Not vulnerable

12.3YT

Vulnerable

12.3YU

Vulnerable

12.3YX

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.3(14)YX2 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.3YZ

Vulnerable

              Affected 12.4-Based Release

              Rebuild

              Maintenance

12.4

SIP ports are closed by default in a release listed below, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.4(3d)

12.4(5b)

12.4(7a)

12.4(8)

12.4MR

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.4(6)MR or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.4SW

Vulnerable; workaround available for all 12.4SW releases where              SIP ports are closed by default

12.4T

SIP ports are closed by default in a release listed below, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.4(2)T5

12.4(4)T3

12.4(6)T1

12.4(9)T

12.4XA

Vulnerable

12.4XB

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.4(4)XB2 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.4XC

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.4(4)XC6* available              12-Feb-07; but routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.4XD

SIP ports are closed by default in 12.4(4)XD2 or later, but              routers running SIP are still vulnerable

12.4XE

Vulnerable; workaround available for all 12.4XE releases where              SIP ports are closed by default

12.4XG

Not vulnerable

12.4XJ

Vulnerable; workaround available for all 12.4XJ releases where              SIP ports are closed by default

12.4XP

Vulnerable; workaround available for all 12.4XP releases where              SIP ports are closed by default

12.4XT

Vulnerable; workaround available for all 12.4XT releases where              SIP ports are closed by default</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">This issue was first reported to Cisco by a customer. There are no  known instances of intentional exploitation of this issue. However, Cisco has  observed data streams that appear to be unintentionally triggering the  vulnerability.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="9">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A stand-alone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy, and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end-users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20070131-sip</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>SIP Packets Reload IOS Devices with support for SIP</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco IOS Voice Service Session Initiated Protocol Denial of Service Vulnerability</Title>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2007-0648</CVE>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>Additional mitigations that can be deployed on Cisco devices within the  network are available in the Cisco Applied Mitigation Bulletin companion  document for this advisory:  https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoAppliedMitigationBulletin/cisco-amb-20070131-sip ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoAppliedMitigationBulletin/cisco-amb-20070131-sip"].
  Disable SIP listening ports
For devices which do not require SIP to be enabled, the simplest and  most effective workaround is to disable SIP processing on the device with the  following commands.

  Warning: When applying this workaround to devices  which are processing MGCP or H.323 calls, the device will not allow you to stop  SIP processing while active calls are being processed. Under these  circumstances, this workaround should be implemented during a maintenance  window when active calls can be briefly stopped.


Enter configuration commands, one per line.  End with CNTL/Z.
Router(config)#sip-ua  Router(config-sip-ua)#no transport udp  Router(config-sip-ua)#no transport tcp  Router(config-sip-ua)#end

After applying this workaround the commands show ip  sockets and show tcp brief all will  not show the device listening on UDP and TCP port 5060:


Router#show ip sockets
Proto    Remote      Port      Local       Port  In Out Stat TTY   17   --listen--          9.13.32.18       2887   0   0   11   0    Router#show tcp brief all  TCB       Local Address           Foreign Address        (state)  6649A5A4  *.1720                  *.*                    LISTEN  66CDC764  *.1723                  *.*                    LISTEN
    Control Plane Policing
For devices which do not need to run SIP, you can use Control Plane  Policing (CoPP) to block all SIP access to the device. Cisco IOS software  releases 12.0S, 12.2SX, 12.2S, 12.3T, 12.4, and 12.4T support the CoPP feature.  CoPP may be configured on a device to protect the management and control planes  to minimize the risk and effectiveness of direct infrastructure attacks by  explicitly permitting only authorized traffic sent to infrastructure devices in  accordance with existing security policies and configurations. The following  example can be adapted to your network.

  Warning: Because SIP utilizes UDP as a transport, it  is possible to spoof the sender's IP address, which may defeat ACLs that permit  communication to these ports from trusted IP addresses.



!-- Permit all TCP and UDP SIP traffic sent to all IP addresses  !-- configured on all interfaces of the affected device so that it  !-- will be policed and dropped by the CoPP feature.      access-list 100 permit tcp any any eq 5060  access-list 100 permit udp any any eq 5060      !-- Permit (Police or Drop)/Deny (Allow) all other Layer3 and Layer4  !-- traffic in accordance with existing security policies and  !-- configurations for traffic that is authorized to be sent  !-- to infrastructure devices.        !-- Create a Class-Map for traffic to be policed by  !-- the CoPP feature.      class-map match-all drop-sip-class    match access-group 100      !-- Create a Policy-Map that will be applied to the  !-- Control-Plane of the device.      policy-map drop-sip-traffic    class drop-sip-class      drop      !-- Apply the Policy-Map to the Control-Plane of the  !-- device.      control-plane    service-policy input drop-sip-traffic

In the above CoPP example, the access control list entries (ACEs) which  match the potential exploit packets with the "permit" action result in these  packets being discarded by the policy-map "drop" function, while packets that  match the "deny" action (not shown) are not affected by the policy-map drop  function. Additional information on the configuration and use of the CoPP  feature can be found at  http://www.cisco.com/en/US/prod/collateral/iosswrel/ps6537/ps6586/ps6642/prod_white_paper0900aecd804fa16a.html ["http://www.cisco.com/en/US/prod/collateral/iosswrel/ps6537/ps6586/ps6642/prod_white_paper0900aecd804fa16a.html"]  and  http://www.cisco.com/en/US/docs/ios/12_3t/12_3t4/feature/guide/gtrtlimt.html ["http://www.cisco.com/en/US/docs/ios/12_3t/12_3t4/feature/guide/gtrtlimt.html"].</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20070131-sip</URL>
        <Description>SIP Packets Reload IOS Devices with support for SIP</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
