<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cvrf:cvrfdoc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:cvrf-common="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/common" xmlns:cvrf="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/cvrf">
  <cvrf:DocumentTitle>Cisco Identity Services Engine Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities</cvrf:DocumentTitle>
  <cvrf:DocumentType>Cisco Security Advisory</cvrf:DocumentType>
  <cvrf:DocumentPublisher Type="Vendor">
    <cvrf:ContactDetails>Emergency Support:
+1 877 228 7302 (toll-free within North America)
+1 408 525 6532 (International direct-dial)
Non-emergency Support:
Email: psirt@cisco.com
Support requests that are received via e-mail are typically acknowledged within 48 hours.</cvrf:ContactDetails>
    <cvrf:IssuingAuthority>Cisco product security incident response is the responsibility of the Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT). The Cisco PSIRT is a dedicated, global team that manages the receipt, investigation, and public reporting of security vulnerability information that is related to Cisco products and networks. The on-call Cisco PSIRT works 24x7 with Cisco customers, independent security researchers, consultants, industry organizations, and other vendors to identify possible security issues with Cisco products and networks.
More information can be found in Cisco Security Vulnerability Policy available at http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html</cvrf:IssuingAuthority>
  </cvrf:DocumentPublisher>
  <cvrf:DocumentTracking>
    <cvrf:Identification>
      <cvrf:ID>cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6</cvrf:ID>
    </cvrf:Identification>
    <cvrf:Status>Final</cvrf:Status>
    <cvrf:Version>2.2</cvrf:Version>
    <cvrf:RevisionHistory>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>1.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-06-25T15:58:17</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Initial public release.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>2.0</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-07-16T15:57:26</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated Cisco ISE code fix, added CVE-2025-20337, and added CSCwp02814.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>2.1</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-07-21T18:03:51</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Updated to indicate active exploitation attempts in the wild.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
      <cvrf:Revision>
        <cvrf:Number>2.2</cvrf:Number>
        <cvrf:Date>2025-07-24T23:30:31</cvrf:Date>
        <cvrf:Description>Added the CVEs for which exploitation attempts have been observed.</cvrf:Description>
      </cvrf:Revision>
    </cvrf:RevisionHistory>
    <cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>2025-06-25T16:00:00</cvrf:InitialReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>2025-07-24T23:30:31</cvrf:CurrentReleaseDate>
    <cvrf:Generator>
      <cvrf:Engine>TVCE</cvrf:Engine>
      <cvrf:Date>2025-08-01T16:05:38.4742562Z</cvrf:Date>
    </cvrf:Generator>
  </cvrf:DocumentTracking>
  <cvrf:DocumentNotes>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Summary" Type="Summary" Ordinal="1">Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Cisco ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to issue commands on the underlying operating system as the root user.

For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.

Cisco has released software updates that address these vulnerabilities. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

Note: Since the publication of version 1.0 of this advisory, improved fixed releases have become available. Cisco recommends upgrading to an enhanced fixed release as follows:

If Cisco ISE is running Release 3.4 Patch 2, no further action is necessary.
If Cisco ISE is running Release 3.3 Patch 6, additional fixes are available in Release 3.3 Patch 7, and the device must be upgraded.
If Cisco ISE has either hot patch ise-apply-CSCwo99449_3.3.0.430_patch4-SPA.tar.gz or hot patch ise-apply-CSCwo99449_3.4.0.608_patch1-SPA.tar.gz installed, Cisco recommends upgrading to Release 3.3 Patch 7 or Release 3.4 Patch 2. The hot patches did not address CVE-2025-20337 and have been deferred from CCO.

This advisory is available at the following link:
https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6 ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6"]</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerable Products" Type="General" Ordinal="2">CVE-2025-20281 and CVE-2025-20337: These vulnerabilities affect Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC releases 3.3 and 3.4, regardless of device configuration. These vulnerabilities do not affect Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC Release 3.2 or earlier.

CVE-2025-20282: This vulnerability affects only Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC Release 3.4, regardless of device configuration. This vulnerability does not affect Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC Release 3.3 or earlier.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Products Confirmed Not Vulnerable" Type="General" Ordinal="3">Only products listed in the Vulnerable Products ["#vp"] section of this advisory are known to be affected by these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Details" Type="General" Ordinal="4">The vulnerabilities are not dependent on one another. Exploitation of one of the vulnerabilities is not required to exploit another vulnerability. In addition, a software release that is affected by one of the vulnerabilities may not be affected by the other vulnerabilities.

Details about the vulnerabilities are as follows:

CVE-2025-20281 and CVE-2025-20337: Cisco ISE API Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities

Multiple vulnerabilities in a specific API of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as root. The attacker does not require any valid credentials to exploit these vulnerabilities.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by submitting a crafted API request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain root privileges on an affected device.

Cisco has released software updates that address these vulnerabilities. There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.

Bug ID(s): CSCwo99449 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwo99449"] and CSCwp02814 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwp02814"]
CVE ID: CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20337
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Critical
CVSS Base Score: 10.0
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H

CVE-2025-20282: Cisco ISE API Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerability

A vulnerability in an internal API of Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device and then execute those files on the underlying operating system as root.

This vulnerability is due a lack of file validation checks that would prevent uploaded files from being placed in privileged directories on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted file to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the affected system and then execute arbitrary code or obtain root privileges on the system.

Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.
Bug ID(s): CSCwp02821 ["https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/CSCwp02821"]
CVE ID: CVE-2025-20282
Security Impact Rating (SIR): Critical
CVSS Base Score: 10.0
CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Workarounds" Type="General" Ordinal="5">There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Fixed Software" Type="General" Ordinal="6">Cisco has released free software updates ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#ssu"] that address the vulnerability described in this advisory. Customers with service contracts that entitle them to regular software updates should obtain security fixes through their usual update channels.

Customers may only install and expect support for software versions and feature sets for which they have purchased a license. By installing, downloading, accessing, or otherwise using such software upgrades, customers agree to follow the terms of the Cisco software license:
https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/end-user-license-agreement.html ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/end-user-license-agreement.html"]

Additionally, customers may only download software for which they have a valid license, procured from Cisco directly, or through a Cisco authorized reseller or partner. In most cases this will be a maintenance upgrade to software that was previously purchased. Free security software updates do not entitle customers to a new software license, additional software feature sets, or major revision upgrades.

The Cisco Support and Downloads page ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/index.html"] on Cisco.com provides information about licensing and downloads. This page can also display customer device support coverage for customers who use the My Devices tool.

When considering software upgrades ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"], customers are advised to regularly consult the advisories for Cisco products, which are available from the Cisco Security Advisories page ["https://www.cisco.com/go/psirt"], to determine exposure and a complete upgrade solution.

In all cases, customers should ensure that the devices to be upgraded contain sufficient memory and confirm that current hardware and software configurations will continue to be supported properly by the new release. If the information is not clear, customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) or their contracted maintenance providers.
  Customers Without Service Contracts
Customers who purchase directly from Cisco but do not hold a Cisco service contract and customers who make purchases through third-party vendors but are unsuccessful in obtaining fixed software through their point of sale should obtain upgrades by contacting the Cisco TAC: https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/web/tsd-cisco-worldwide-contacts.html ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/web/tsd-cisco-worldwide-contacts.html"]

Customers should have the product serial number available and be prepared to provide the URL of this advisory as evidence of entitlement to a free upgrade.
      Fixed Releases
Customers are advised to upgrade to an appropriate fixed software release ["https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/resources/security_vulnerability_policy.html#fixes"] as indicated in the following table.

Note: Since the publication of version 1.0 of this advisory, improved fixed releases have become available. Cisco recommends upgrading to an enhanced fixed release as follows:

If Cisco ISE is running Release 3.4 Patch 2, no further action is necessary.
If Cisco ISE is running Release 3.3 Patch 6, additional fixes are available in Release 3.3 Patch 7, and the device must be upgraded.
If Cisco ISE has either hot patch ise-apply-CSCwo99449_3.3.0.430_patch4-SPA.tar.gz or hot patch ise-apply-CSCwo99449_3.4.0.608_patch1-SPA.tar.gz installed, Cisco recommends upgrading to Release 3.3 Patch 7 or Release 3.4 Patch 2. The hot patches did not address CVE-2025-20337 and have been deferred from CCO.
        Cisco ISE or ISE-PIC Release  First Fixed Release for CVE-2025-20281  First Fixed Release for CVE-2025-20282  First Fixed Release for CVE-2025-20337          3.2 and earlier  Not vulnerable  Not vulnerable  Not vulnerable      3.3  3.3 Patch 7  Not vulnerable  3.3 Patch 7      3.4  3.4 Patch 2  3.4 Patch 2  3.4 Patch 2
For instructions on upgrading a device, see the Upgrade Guides on the Cisco Identity Service Engine ["https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/security/identity-services-engine/series.html"] support page.

The Cisco Product Security Incident Response Team (PSIRT) validates only the affected and fixed release information that is documented in this advisory.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Vulnerability Policy" Type="General" Ordinal="7">To learn about Cisco security vulnerability disclosure policies and publications, see the Security Vulnerability Policy ["http://www.cisco.com/web/about/security/psirt/security_vulnerability_policy.html"]. This document also contains instructions for obtaining fixed software and receiving security vulnerability information from Cisco.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Exploitation and Public Announcements" Type="General" Ordinal="8">In July 2025, the Cisco PSIRT became aware of attempted exploitation of CVE-2025-20281 and CVE-2025-20337 in the wild. Cisco continues to strongly recommend that customers upgrade to a fixed software release to remediate these vulnerabilities.</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Source" Type="General" Ordinal="9">Cisco would like to thank the following people for reporting these vulnerabilities:

Bobby Gould of Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative: CVE-2025-20281
Kentaro Kawane of GMO Cybersecurity by Ierae, working with Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative: CVE-2025-20282 and CVE-2025-20337</cvrf:Note>
    <cvrf:Note Title="Legal Disclaimer" Type="Legal Disclaimer" Ordinal="10">THIS DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND DOES NOT IMPLY ANY KIND OF GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE. YOUR USE OF THE INFORMATION ON THE DOCUMENT OR MATERIALS LINKED FROM THE DOCUMENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CISCO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS DOCUMENT AT ANY TIME.

A standalone copy or paraphrase of the text of this document that omits the distribution URL is an uncontrolled copy and may lack important information or contain factual errors. The information in this document is intended for end users of Cisco products.</cvrf:Note>
  </cvrf:DocumentNotes>
  <cvrf:DocumentReferences>
    <cvrf:Reference Type="Self">
      <cvrf:URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6</cvrf:URL>
      <cvrf:Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities</cvrf:Description>
    </cvrf:Reference>
  </cvrf:DocumentReferences>
  <ProductTree xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/prod">
    <Branch Type="Vendor" Name="Cisco">
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco Identity Services Engine Software">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-111903">Cisco Identity Services Engine Software </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
      <Branch Type="Product Name" Name="Cisco ISE Passive Identity Connector">
        <FullProductName ProductID="CVRFPID-292424">Cisco ISE Passive Identity Connector </FullProductName>
      </Branch>
    </Branch>
  </ProductTree>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="1" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco Identity Services Engine Unauthenticated File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwp02821</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwp02821</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2025-20282</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>10.0</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="2" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco ISE API Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwo99449</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwo99449</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2025-20281</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>10.0</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
  <Vulnerability Ordinal="3" xmlns="http://docs.oasis-open.org/csaf/ns/csaf-cvrf/v1.2/vuln">
    <Title>Cisco ISE API Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</Title>
    <ID SystemName="Cisco Bug ID">CSCwp02814</ID>
    <Notes>
      <Note Title="Cisco Bug IDs" Type="Other" Ordinal="1">CSCwp02814</Note>
      <Note Title="Affected Product Comprehensiveness" Type="Other" Ordinal="2">Complete.</Note>
    </Notes>
    <CVE>CVE-2025-20337</CVE>
    <ProductStatuses>
      <Status Type="Known Affected">
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-111903</ProductID>
        <ProductID>CVRFPID-292424</ProductID>
      </Status>
    </ProductStatuses>
    <CVSSScoreSets>
      <ScoreSetV3>
        <BaseScoreV3>10.0</BaseScoreV3>
        <VectorV3>CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H</VectorV3>
      </ScoreSetV3>
    </CVSSScoreSets>
    <Remediations>
      <Remediation Type="Workaround">
        <Description>There are no workarounds that address these vulnerabilities.</Description>
      </Remediation>
    </Remediations>
    <References>
      <Reference Type="Self">
        <URL>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-unauth-rce-ZAd2GnJ6</URL>
        <Description>Cisco Identity Services Engine Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities</Description>
      </Reference>
    </References>
  </Vulnerability>
</cvrf:cvrfdoc>
